This stock has shown good strength and if you
look at today's volumes on the daily chart, the
volumes are much better than the average of the last few days. The momentum can remain positive here.
So buy ICC Loba
below 2040 with a stop loss below 2140
for targets around 2270. Now that all these
trades are complete, let's talk about the ban. Many
stocks are preparing to be banned.
These five stocks will be banned if the situation remains the same at this time.
Chambal
Fertilizers,
SAIL, Hindustan Aeronautical Dixon Tech and Lako.
These five stocks are preparing to be banned.
I am checking some data. If
it turns out to be correct, I will
discuss it shortly. But before that, let's check a chart.
This stock of ICICI Lord is
closing at its day high. Today morning, your call was on
this. Should I carry this position?
Of course, I will carry it. I think there is
a BTS here.